onecoin.eu 2015-03-15

# OneCoin / Privacy policy

The following privacy procedures apply to One Network Services Limited (OneCoin):

**Personal Information**

Onecoin only collects personal information when you request our services and only uses the information collected to provide those services for you. Onecoin will also collect and store the name and Internet Protocol (IP) address of the server you are using to access our website, the date and time the visit at the website was made and the information which you are accessing.

If you choose to make a purchase, you will be asked to provide contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and financial information. This information is used for billing purposes and to process your order. Onecoin handles all of this data with the utmost confidentiality.

**Third Parties**

Any personal information provided will not be traded, rented, sold or otherwise shared with anyone outside of the Onecoin group, or used for reasons beyond those contemplated in this statement. From time to time, we may engage third parties to process your information on our behalf; however, none of Onecoin affiliates  have permission to retain, share, store or use personal information for any reason other than providing the requested service.

**Cookies**

www.onecoin.eu relies on “cookie” technology to allow you to re-access your registered account profile during a web session. This mechanism is employed solely for your convenience and for no other purpose.

"Cookies” are small bits of text that are either used for the duration of a session (“session cookies”) or saved on a user’s hard drive in order to identify that user, or information about that user, the next time the user logs on the a Web site (“persistent cookies”).

**Security**

The website takes every precaution to protect our visitor’s information. When visitors submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and off-line.

We at Onecoin do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our Members’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a locked facility.

If visitors have any questions about the security on www.Onecoin.eu, feel free to contact the customer service.

To prevent unauthorized access, disclosure and improper use of your information, we have established appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to protect the information we collect in accordance with our privacy policy.

**IP Addresses and Cookies**

Onecoin may collect information about computers, including IP addresses, operating systems and browser types where available, for system administration purposes. This is statistical data about customers' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

For the same reason as above, the Onecoin may obtain information about general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of the computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to the computer's hard drive. Such cookies help Onecoin to improve the Website and to deliver better and more personalised services. They enable Onecoin to estimate its audience size and usage pattern, to store information about customer preferences, such as wagering patterns, and to recognise Account Holders when they return to the Website. 

An Account Holder may refuse to accept cookies by activating a setting on the browser which allows one to refuse the setting of cookies. Activating such setting however may mean that the Account Holder may be unable to access certain parts of the Website.

**Storage of Personal Data**

All information submitted to Onecoin is stored and kept on secure servers. While the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure, any payment transactions and submissions of personal information is transmitted using SSL encryption technology. Onecoin shall do its utmost to protect personal data, but any transmission of data is at the users own risk. Once Onecoin has received any personal information, strict procedures and security features will be used to prevent unauthorised access.
